Aaron

Byrne

Computer Science and Business Student

T: 087 1724488

E: aaonbyrneo56@gmail.com



PROFILE

A Computer Science and Business student competent in Experience with Frameworks such as React and NodeJS libraries such as Express from college projects and groupwork. Highly analytical, with a spectrum of skills gained from university projects and experience in global companies. Possessing a solid background in customer-focused roles, leveraging confident interpersonal skills and a mature outlook, with a broad interest in the tech and finance sector.



STRENGTHS

Programming
Problem Solving
Analysis
Communication
Team Collaboration
Prioritisation
Commercially Aware
Numerically Astute
Client Service



IT SKILLS

Microsoft Office Java, C++, JavaScript ReactJS, SQL NodeJS, Git Algorithms Data Structures

EDUCATION

2019-present

B.A. (Moderatorship) Honours Bachelor's Degree Computer Science and **Business**– Trinity College Dublin

Key modules: Algorithms and Data Structures, Software Engineering, Computer Networks, Investments, Accounting, Finance, Economics, Applied Probability, Maths, Marketing, Natural Language Processing

2019 **Leaving Certificate (522 points)-** CBS Lucan. 2019 Student of the year.

EXPERIENCE

Compliance Intern (June 2021 – September 2021)

BioMarin Pharmaceutical Inc.

BioMarin is a world leader in developing and commercializing innovative biopharmaceuticals for rare diseases driven by genetic causes.

- Preparing Distribution Compliance documentation including Country Specifications, QTAs etc.
- Reviewing temperature excursions on global shipments and assessing if there is a product impact.
- Preparing PowerPoint presentations for team and cross-functional updates relating to Distribution Compliance projects.
- Engage with global stakeholders and build relationships with Logistics, Product Launch, QA CMO, Commercial Operations, Customer Service etc.
- Play a key role in audit readiness, preparation, and support for both the Shanbally and Dublin offices.
- Adept at building a friendly and professional rapport with stakeholders, as well as being an active and productive member of the team.

Online Department (November 2019-January 2020)

Brown Thomas, Dublin.

- Processed and prepared packages ordered from the Brown Thomas online store to be made ready for delivery.
- Helped manage and organise stock in terms of size and brand in the stockroom and on the shop floor.
- Helped customers with questions and any assistance they needed.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Self-employed Personal Shopper (November 2020- February 2020)

BuyMie, Dublin

- Picked and purchased groceries specifically chosen by users using the BuyMie app.
- Delivered orders to their door with excellent care and caution.

Product Finisher (Summer of 2017, 2018 and 2019)

CoverUp Ltd. Clondalkin

- Assisting in the day-to-day operations of the printing company.
- Measure, cut, finish signs, flags, banners, and covers.
- Take in and organise new stock as well as packaging and preparing outgoing deliveries.

INTERESTS and ACHIEVEMENTS

Player for Esker Celtic FC | Music (guitar and piano player) | Tech Enthusiast

- Demonstrator for Intro to Programming. Assist first year students with any questions they have relating to their coursework.
- Esker Celtic Player of the Year 2018
- CBS Lucan Student of the Year 2019
- 6th Year Business Student of the Year

REFEREE DETAILS AVAILABLE ON REQUEST